[{
"difficulty": "easy",
"subject": "cs",
"playerWon": "true",
"playerRecords": [
	{
		"question": "What type of language is XML?",
		"answer": "Markup",
		"userAnswer": "markup",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 4.8465734
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the main function of a firewall?",
		"answer": "Security",
		"userAnswer": "safety",
		"confidence": 1,
		"timeTaken": 8.320208
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Git used for?",
		"answer": "Version control",
		"userAnswer": "version control",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 3.7722597
	},
	{
		"question": "What is an IDE used for?",
		"answer": "Development",
		"userAnswer": "development",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 3.4025545
	},
	{
		"question": "What type of memory is RAM?",
		"answer": "Volatile",
		"userAnswer": "volatile",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 5.5746913
	},
	{
		"question": "What is SQL used for in databases?",
		"answer": "Querying",
		"userAnswer": "data management",
		"confidence": 3,
		"timeTaken": 5.8737698
	},
	{
		"question": "What does CPU execute?",
		"answer": "Instructions",
		"userAnswer": "instructions",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 3.7525187
	},
	{
		"question": "What do routers do with data?",
		"answer": "Forwarding",
		"userAnswer": "idk",
		"confidence": 1,
		"timeTaken": 5.602336
	},
	{
		"question": "What does Wi-Fi provide for devices?",
		"answer": "Connectivity",
		"userAnswer": "internet connection",
		"confidence": 3,
		"timeTaken": 8.203376
	},
	{
		"question": "What type of network is LAN?",
		"answer": "Local",
		"userAnswer": "local",
		"confidence": 3,
		"correctness": true,
		"timeTaken": 2.6525073
	}
],
"totalPoints": 8100
}]